campusclarity.com 2015-09-11

# Privacy Policy | CampusClarity

_Data Collected by CampusClarity_

CampusClarity, a service of LawRoom, collects two types of data from our users: (1) personal data and (2) non-personal data.

**Personal Data**

We collect personal data to identify our users and to track their site usage. We collect the following personally identifiable information on our users:

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Student ID

We use this data to verify who our users are, to send announcements and reminders, and to monitor user progress and performance in our courses.

Additionally, CampusClarity collects demographic information from users, as well as their course usage and progress information. Demographic information may include users’ age, gender, sexual orientation, relationship status, year, home state, housing, ethnicity, and affiliations. Course usage, progress, and performance information includes the courses users have been assigned, when they’ve accessed the course, the portions of the course that the user has completed, and aggregate measures relating to their course performance. CampusClarity stores this information along with users’ personal data.

**Non-Personal Data**

We also collect non-personal data to improve and support our services, provide reports to schools, and develop new products. Specifically, we collect user responses to questions in our courses, course survey information, and other technical data. We use this non-personal data to develop and refine our courses, and to provide information to help schools improve their harm-reduction programs.

User responses include the answers users provide to questions in our courses. Throughout our courses, users answer personal questions about drug and alcohol use, sexual activity, attitudes, and beliefs. We store this information anonymously. We store each users’ demographic information along with these responses, but this data is de-identified. So, it is impossible for CampusClarity to determine any identifiable user’s response to a question contained in any of our courses.

At the end of the course users are asked to rate the course, and they have the option to type comments about the course. This information is stored anonymously along with the de-identified user data.

We share all this data with schools to help them improve their harm-reduction programs. Whenever we report answers, we report data in such a way that no individual student’s responses can be identified. We also use this data to improve our courses.

We also collect the following technical data anonymously:

  * IP addresses
  * Browser types
  * Device information

We log IP addresses for systems administration purposes. IP addresses are logged to track a user’s session and help us determine how often the areas of our site are visited. We periodically view and discard the information. We do not link IP addresses to specific users.

**FERPA & Personal Data**

Personally identifiable student data may constitute a confidential education record for the purposes of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy act of 1974 (“FERPA”), 20 U.S.C. § 1232 et seq. as amended, and related regulations, 34 C.F.R. section 99.1 et seq.

CampusClarity complies with FERPA when dealing with personally identifiable user data. Unless required by law, we will not sell, share, disclose, or give away personally identifiable User data to any third party not otherwise associated or allied with CampusClarity or a user’s school.  
Cookies

A cookie is a small file created by your Web browser to assign a unique identification to your computer. We do not use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer. To use CampusClarity, you must have the cookies option of your browser turned on.

**Do Not Track Notice**

CampusClarity does not track its users across third party websites, nor does it allow third parties to collect personally identifiable information on CampusClarity pages. As such, our service does not respond to browser “Do Not Track” requests.

**Third Party Sites**

CampusClarity includes links to third party sites unaffiliated with our course. CampusClarity is not responsible for the content on these sites. Please check the privacy statements on these sites for information on their policies. Third parties may not collect personally identifiable information when a user accesses CampusClarity’s website.  
Children’s Privacy

CampusClarity respects the privacy of children. Our website and courses are not for use by children under the age of 15, and children under the age of 13 are not permitted to use this website or our training courses. For more information, see our Terms of Use.

**Contact Us**

If you have questions about this privacy policy, or if you want to make changes to data provided during the user registration process, contact us by email at admin@campusclarity.com.  
Changes to this Policy

CampusClarity has the right to change this privacy policy at any time if we so choose. If we make a significant change to our privacy policy, we will update this webpage and post a notice on our homepage so users can review the change.

**Effective Date**

The effective date of this policy is April 8, 2014.
